{
    "riddles": [{
            "round": "1",
            "number": "0",
            "question": "I have a ring, but no hands. I used to be plugged into the wall but now I follow you every where. What am I?",
            "answer": "Telephone"

        },

        {
            "round": "1",
            "number": "1",
            "question": "What season does Humpty Dumpty hate the most?",
            "answer": "Fall"

        },

        {
            "round": "1",
            "number": "2",
            "question": "I am black when clean and white when dirty. What am I?",
            "answer": "Blackboard"

        },
        {
            "round": "1",
            "number": "3",
            "question": "What runs around a house but does not move?",
            "answer": "Fence"

        },
        {
            "round": "1",
            "number": "4",
            "question": "Once you have it, you want to share it. Once you share it, you don’t have it. What is it?",
            "answer": "Secret"

        },
        {
            "round": "1",
            "number": "5",
            "question": "I start with M and end with X. I have a never ending amount of letters. What am I?",
            "answer": "Mailbox"

        }, {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "0",
            "question": "What can elephants make that no other animals can make?",
            "answer": "Elephants"

        },

        {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "1",
            "question": "I have a head & no body, but I do have a tail. What am I?",
            "answer": "Coin"

        },

        {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "2",
            "question": "What do you call a bear without an ear?",
            "answer": "B"

        },
        {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "3",
            "question": "I can be made and I can be played. I can be cracked and I can be told. What am I?",
            "answer": "Joke"

        },
        {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "4",
            "question": "What has a bed but doesn’ t sleep and a mouth but never eats ? ",
            "answer" : "River"

        },
        {
            "round": "2",
            "number": "5",
            "question": "I am a container with no sides and no lid, yet golden treasure lays inside. What am I?",
            "answer": "Egg"

        }, {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "0",
            "question": "Which letter of the alphabet contains the most water?",
            "answer": "C"

        },

        {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "1",
            "question": "What has a soul but doesn’t live and a tongue but can’t taste?",
            "answer": "Shoe"

        },

        {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "2",
            "question": "You buy me to eat, but never eat me. What am I?",
            "answer": "Silverware"

        },
        {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "3",
            "question": "What ends everything always?",
            "answer": "G"

        },
        {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "4",
            "question": "The maker doesn’t want it, the buyer doesn’t use it and the user doesn’t know it. What is it?",
            "answer": "Coffin"

        },
        {
            "round": "3",
            "number": "5",
            "question": "You go at red and stop at green. What am I?",
            "answer": "Watermelon"

        }
    ]
}
